What do you mean?
Exactly what I said.
You're being transferred to the Dualium Mining Department.
But why so suddenly?
You should have read the report I submitted previously.
Hm?
Oh, yes.
That report about the relationship between entertainment and labor efficiency.
Hm.
Yes, it was very interesting to hear the opinions of someone working in the field.
I was promised it would be shown to higher-ups.
Yeah.
At Zodiac's direct request.
We're counting on you.
What do you mean, Zodiac?
Interesting.
Oh, and by the way,
I heard the DES has taken over Akibasta recently.
You know that for sure?
I'm surprised you didn't know.
What about AKB-0048?
Who knows?
But I'm sure they'll be captured soon.
Keep your chin up.
After all, you'll get to see your daughter soon.
Give her my regards when you visit her in prison, won't you?
Akibasta fell to the DES?
Yeah.
It should be on the news before too long.
Hm.
It can't be.
That couldn't have happened to Zero Zero.
Thank you all.
Fuck.
進むための力にする
心折れそうな長い桜の前
未来があるなら背を向けられない
友よ覚えているかい?
あの日違い合ったこの場所
季節の花が咲く
I'll see you next time.
Yes, sir. Also, the disappearance of the ninth generation, Yuko Oshima, has been confirmed, but unfortunately, we were unable to control the energy released when she became the Santa Nova.
What an ill-mannered Santa Nova. Midsommar makes her restless.
AKB-0048 and your daughter's whereabouts are currently unknown to us at this time.
Chieri is a lucky child.
Yes, of course. It really is her. Chieri is my shining star.
Kira, drive gone. Engine's failing. We can't determine our coordinates.
So we're broken down and lost to boot.
We escaped from that situation, so be thankful for that much.
It could have been worse. Much worse.
Here.
I'm gonna look around a bit.
How's Tomi-chin and Kochi-haru? Are they… Did they get captured by the DES?
They're okay. They evacuated to the shrine.
Are the people of Aki-basta all right?
The DES is after Zero-Zero. It's more dangerous for us to stay there.
That means they shouldn't harm civilians any further.
Yuko-san.
What about you, Ko-san?
Question.
Anna?
Is it true that Mi-chan was leading the DES in their attack on Aki-basta?
It seems to be.
Why would she do that?
Tsubasa-san.
I have a request to make.
Oh, hello. Time to torture me?
You are fifth-generation Minami Minagishi. You are the Center Nova.
Kanasa, calm down.
Was I?
I wonder if I was actually a true Center Nova.
I don't know. I was scared. I ran away while it was happening.
Huh?
You ran away?
Are you saying the Center Nova's vanished?
All of them were trapped in some other dimension?
If I had kept performing, I'd be trapped too.
Does everyone who becomes a Center Nova go to some other world?
No.
Most people just graduate.
Nothing like that ever happened to them.
Conditions for triggering the Center Nova phenomenon and the disappearances are different.
The three conditions for triggering the phenomenon are a concert on Aki-basta, a violent storm, and finally, a battle during a concert.
But for someone to vanish, the Center Nova must rise to their pinnacle.
They must continue to shine even brighter until the moment they obtain the ultimate light.
In that instant, you vanish into the other world.
Then is Yuko-san in that other world?
She's probably there. In a world with Ah-chan and the others.
Oh, she's alive. Yuko-san is alive.
But what about the ones that didn't vanish?
If your desire to shine wavers for even a moment, then you lose the ultimate light.
And I never tried to get it back.
In order to disappear, the Center Nova must always look upwards and continue climbing.
I was afraid, so I stopped.
So you graduated instead?
Yes. That's exactly what I did.
I immediately abandoned the name Minami Minigishi and fled.
I didn't even perform a graduation concert.
Why did you become a photographer?
I did.
To protect you, I wanted to stay with Zero-Zero and prevent anyone else from disappearing.
Guess I failed, huh?
Okay, so why did you have the DES attack Akibuster at all?
Because.
My father must have something to do with this.
Dualium.
Discovered in the beginning of the 21st century, this unknown substance had a certain unique power.
You want me to take pictures of rocks?
I specialize in girls, not boulders.
By opening gates in space-time, it connects our world to the one on the other side.
An alternate dimension, if you prefer.
What is the world on the other side?
Why ask me, you've already seen it first-hand, Mee-chan.
Former Center Nova and fifth generation Minami Minigishi.
A pleasure to meet you.
Charming.
Now then, while researching Dualium, we stumbled upon a new life.
A breed of hyperspace creatures.
Show her.
Kirara?
Dualium and the Kiraras.
Using these two things, the Tsukubo Research Facility successfully developed the first method of interplanetary travel in human history.
The Kirara Drive.
Kiraras respond to a select force.
The will or souls of certain people.
And the people they connect with have their power amplified.
You don't mean…
Yes.
Idols.
In ancient times, long before idols existed,
the arts were sacred rituals performed to connect the gods and other worlds.
If I'm right,
it may somehow be related to this.
So, the reason the DES has been trying to capture Zero-Zero alive is…
To use you and the Kiraras for military purposes.
Oh, I guess that makes sense.
The Center Nova can't make Kiraras shine brighter than anyone else.
And Akibastar has the largest deposit of Dualium discovered.
I told Zodiac about the Dualium in Akibastar, and that a new Center Nova might be born.
That's why they attacked with such overwhelming force.
And the result…
Because of you, Akibastar is…
Where are you going?
I'm going to talk to my father.
You can't do that, Chiyari!
But…
Chiyari, calm down.
Why, Mi-chan?
I thought you wanted to protect the other members!
Answer me!
She wanted to try rescuing the Center Novus who had already disappeared.
Rescue them?
The moment someone becomes a Center Novus,
she wanted to try rescuing the Center Novus who had already disappeared.
Rescue them?
The moment someone becomes a Center Novus,
a gate connecting our world to the other side opens up.
Mi-chan thought she could pass through that gate
and reach Ah-chan and the other missing Center Novus.
That's why she helped Zodiac and waited for her chance.
But she was deceived by Zodiac.
I'm not surprised that happened to her.
But I always thought she'd just end up with a bad boyfriend, not destroy a planet.
Isn't it possible that she's just a traitor?
No, it isn't.
How can you be so sure?
Because…
I'm the same way.
I want…
so badly to rescue the girls we've lost.
I want to see Ah-chan.
Sabasa-san…
She's not the only one.
Sensei-sensei may have been thinking the same thing.
Sensei-sensei too?
Yes.
That's why he revived the general elections,
and attempted to create a new Center Nova.
Is it possible to save her?
If someone becomes the Center Nova,
can we save Yuko-san and the other girls?
Yes, it's possible.
No!
A barrier!
Have we established communication with Sensei-sensei?
Not yet.
We're still trying.
We can't get in touch with Woda, either.
What should we do?
It's getting dangerous.
End the transmission.
Yes, ma'am.
Do the Center Nova's…
Or Ah-chan?
Are you absolutely certain they want to be rescued?
Do you really trust Mii-chan?
Are you sure it's wise?
I was the seventh generation Shinoda Maruko.
Nothing will ever change that fact.
Once you accept a name and an ambition,
you can't throw it away so easily.
Suzuko, what are you doing?
I can't… find anything.
What?
I can't find any information about Zero Zero.
Even all the fan pages are gone.
It's like we don't exist.
Do you think the DES erased them?
It's possible.
Or they increased restrictions.
Either way, the end result is painfully obvious.
You mean…
It's over.
Do you think it's gonna end like this?
I hope it doesn't.
I wanted to become an elected member.
I wanted to become a successor.
I see.
Mii-chan… did what she did to save the center novas.
We don't know if it's true.
Remember that.
Kanata…
I don't care if her intentions were purer.
Yeah.
I still don't think I could forgive her.
Chiyori, sorry about earlier.
I shouldn't have said you can't talk to your father.
It's okay.
You were absolutely right.
But still…
I have to think of a way to settle things with him for good.
But to be honest, I don't know how.
I'll figure it out though.
If it's the last thing I do.
Are you worried about Yuko?
Hmm…
I'm thinking…
Well…
Of becoming the center nova.
I'll become the center nova.
Open the gate to the other world.
And save everyone who's been taken away.
You can't do that, Nagisa.
Just becoming the center nova is difficult enough.
You'd be aiming for something beyond that.
It's impossible.
I know…
We don't even know what's going to happen to Zero-Zero.
This may have lost everything.
I know…
But I have to try.
Did they find us?
They must have followed our troops.
I know…
But I have to try…
Did they find us?
They must have followed our troops.
I know…
But I have to try…
I have to try…
Did they find us?
They must have followed our troops.
I know…
Did they find us?
They must have followed our transmission to Akibastar back here.
Tsubasa-san!
Should we prepare for launch?
Since we can't resupply ourselves, we should avoid combat for the time…
We're going to run?
Unmanned enemy units approaching.
Prepare the Kirara drive.
The system has not been fully repaired yet.
We don't know where we'll end up.
It doesn't matter.
We can't afford a fight yet.
Activate the drive now.
Energy at 85%.
Five minutes until activation.
Huh?
A D.E.F. attack?
We are currently engaging the D.E.F.
Five minutes until emergency Kirara drive activated.
Four minutes and fifty seconds remaining!
If we don't fight back, we're done for!
Tsubasa-san!
The Hegar hatch is open and L.A.S. is launching!
Who is it?
Mishan?
It's Mishan!
She's running!
Maybe she's the one who told the D.E.F. we're here!
Ugh!
What the…
Goodbye, my AKB.
I'll shine one last time.
Mishan!
Get back aboard this ship right now!
Not happening!
This is fifth generation Minami Minogishi's graduation concert.
Better late than never.
At least let me go out with a bang.
I've never known that I've ever known that I've ever known.
In a white room, a young man's world.
Crazy!
Two minutes to go!
Come back now, Minami Mino-san!
Who's piloting the LAS?
I've never known that I've ever known.
Each 100 days of the night is ideal for a moment.
Everyone wants to see the dark powers and Jerusalem.
No!
Mi-chan!
I can't even perform an encore.
I never get to finish anything.
But...
I suppose...
that... suits me.
Takamina!
You're not gonna run again, are you?
We haven't forgiven you, Mi-chan.
But right now, we need all the help we can get.
That... that wasn't half bad.
Thank you for showing us the greatest Zero-Zero piloting techniques of all time.
Awesome!
So cool!
Blam!
Ra-da-da-da!
Boom!
Thank you very much!
Please let me call you my big sister!
I secretly supported you all this time!
Mi-chan!
I wanna save Yuko and the others!
Please, Dave!
We need you, so come back to us!
I'm beat.
I guess I'll have to start over as a trainee.
Takamina, hurry!
I'm beat.
I guess I'll have to start over as a trainee.
Takamina, hurry!
ちょまCO-
Boo!
I'm beat.
I guess I'll have to start over as a trainee...
Takamina, hurry!
You free yours and yours!
Future
Umaia!
Uhhhhhh...
Want to go?
Unit 1
E nationwide
Minucius
If you kill me you and remember
Well...
Um Born
The Mission
The 추가
seventeen
A double
Thank you.
夢などまだ種だった
それくらい時が過ぎ 花は咲くのだろう
この涙を君に捧ぐ もっと君が輝くな
ずっと見守ってた 深奥の空から
今僕は雨になろう
Ah 君に捧ぐ こんなの風に
出来ることは 君の虚しさを
少しでも癒すことさ
僕は雨になろう
もう食べよう
終わり
探索
じゃゃん
追いかける
Thank you.